A Guide to the Richard Harding Davis Collection 1887-1917, n.d.
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Richard Harding Davis Collection 1887-1917, n.d.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
6109-g
This holding consists of 77 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This holding was purchased on November 1, 1964.
Contents List
- Edwin Booth to Lemuel Clarke Davis January 20, 1887, ALS, 1 p. with envelope (Box 15)
- Grover Cleveland to Lemuel Clarke Davis July 5, 1891, ALS, 4 pp. with envelope (Box 15)
- Rebecca Harding Davis to [Richard Harding Davis] [1892], ALS, 8 pp. (Box 15)
- Grover Cleveland to Lemuel Clarke Davis May 4, 1893, ALS, 3 pp. with envelope and a note [by LCD] signed "Dad" (Box 15)
- Henry Arthur Jones to Lemuel Clarke Davis April 7, 1896, ALS, 3 pp. with envelope (Box 15)
- Grover Cleveland to Lemuel Clarke Davis May 5, 1896, ALS, 2 pp. with envelope (Box 15)
- Anthony Hope Hawkins to Richard Harding Davis July 6, 1896, APCS (Box 15)
- Augustin Daly to Lemuel Clarke Davis November 26, 1896, ALS, 3 pp. with envelope (Box 15)
- Justin Huntley McCarthy to Charles Belmont Davis March 31, 1897, ALS, 4 pp. (Box 15)
- Grover Cleveland to Lemuel Clarke Davis July 26, 1897, ALS, 4 pp. with envelope (Box 15)
- Grover Cleveland to Lemuel Clarke Davis (signature excised) December 25, 1900, AL, 4 pp. (Box 15)
- Frances Cleveland to [Rebecca Harding] Davis May 4, 1904, ALS, 4 pp. (Box 15)
- Ellen Terry to L.C.D. [November 26, 1901], ALS, 2 pp. with envelope (Box 15)
  Encloses Ellen Terry to Charles Belmont Davis, ANS, n.d.
- [Walter Appleton] Clark to [Richard Harding] Davis February 16, 1902, ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
  With an in-text illustration
- Joseph Jefferson to Lemuel Clarke Davis July 14, 1902, ALS, 3 pp. with envelope (Box 15)
- Owen Wister to [Richard Harding] Davis November 6, 1902, ALS, 8 pp. (Box 15)
- Grover Cleveland to [Lemuel Clarke] Davis August 23, 1903, ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
- John Hay to Lemuel Clarke Davis October 23, 1903, TLS, 2 pp. with envelope (Box 15)
- John Hay to Lemuel Clarke Davis June 24, 1904, TLS, 1 p., with envelope (Box 15)
- Sarah G. LeMoyne to [Richard Harding] Davis and the Directors of the "Forest Home" [July 26, 1904], ALS, 2 pp. with envelope (Box 15)
  Endorsed by J[oseph] Jefferson
- Grover Cleveland to Lemuel Clarke Davis November 22, 1904, ALS, 4 pp. (Box 15)
- [Rebecca Harding Davis] to [Richard Harding Davis] January 18, 1908, ALS, 8 pp. (Box 15)
- [Rebecca Harding Davis] to [Richard Harding Davis] [1908], ALS, 6 pp. (Box 15)
- [Rebecca Harding Davis] to [Richard Harding Davis] [1909], ALS, 6 pp. (Box 16)
- Brand Whitlock to Richard [Harding Davis] March 5, 1915, ALS, 8 pp. (Box 16)
- [Jean Jules] Jusserand to Richard Harding Davis April 1, 1915, TLS, 2 pp. with envelope (Box 16)
  Enclosed card of Raymond Poincare, marked "thanks," addressed to Richard Harding Davis
- Theodore Roosevelt to Richard Harding Davis May 24, 1915, TLS, 1 p. (Box 16)
- Theodore Roosevelt to Richard Harding Davis October 15, 1915, TLS, 1 p. (Box 16)
- Anthony Hope Hawkins to Richard Harding Davis February 22, 1916, ALS, 1 p. (Box 16)
- Winfield S. Moody to Charles Belmont Davis April 12 [1916], ALS, 2 pp. (Box 16)
- Theodore Roosevelt to Charles Belmont Davis April 12, 1916, Telegram (Box 16)
- Rupert Hughes to Charles Belmont Davis April 13, 1916, ALS, 2 pp. (Box 16)
- James B[rendan] Connolly to [Charles Belmont Davis] April 13 [1916], ALS, 1 p. (Box 16)
- H.J. Whigham to Charles Belmont Davis April 15, 1916, ALS, 3 pp. (Box 16)
- Margaret Jenkins to Charles [Belmont Davis] April 16 [1916], ALS, 1 p. (Box 16)
- Richard Washburn Child to Charles Belmont Davis April 17, [1916], ALS, 1 p. (Box 16)
- C.P. Connolly to Charles Belmont Davis April 17, 1916, TLS, 1 p. (Box 16)
- Mary P. Starr to Charles [Belmont Davis] April 19, 1916, ALS, 3 pp. (Box 16)
- Edmund D. Barron to Charles Belmont Davis April 20, 1916, TLS, 1 p. (Box 16)
- Arthur S[omers] Roche to Charles Belmont Davis April 20, 1916, TLS, 1 p. (Box 16)
- Gouverneur Morris to Charles Belmont Davis April 20, 1916, ALS, 4 pp. with envelope (Box 16)
- May Webster to Charles [Belmont Davis] April 22, 1916, ALS, 3 pp. (Box 16)
- John Fox, Jr. to Charles [Belmont Davis] April 23, 1916, ALS, 3 pp. (Box 16)
- Elizabeth Wall Tripp to Charles Belmont Davis April 24, 1916, ALS, 5 pp. with envelope (Box 16)
- Gouverneur Morris to Charles Belmont Davis April 24, 1916, ALS, 8 pp. with envelope (Box 16)
- Jane Rosetta Slade to [Charles Belmont] Davis May 19 [1916], ALS, 2 pp. (Box 16)
- Ronald Simmons to Charles Belmont Davis May 22, 1916, TLS, 1 p. with envelope (Box 16)
- Lizzie S. Watts to [Charles Belmont] Davis May 25 [1916], ALS, 3 pp. (Box 16)
- Winston Churchill to Charles Belmont Davis June 1, 1916, TLS, 1 p. (Box 16)
- Irvin S[hrewsbury] Cobb to Charles Belmont Davis June 2 [1916], ALS, 1 p. (Box 16)
- John Drew to Charles [Belmont Davis] June 5, 1916, ALS, 2 pp. (Box 16)
- Charles Dana Gibson to Charles Belmont Davis [June 9, 1916], ALS, 4 pp. with envelope (Box 16)
- Anthony Hope Hawkins ot Charles Belmont Davis June 20, 1916, ALS, 3 pp. with envelope (Box 16)
- John T[inney] McCutcheon to Charles Belmont Davis [June 28, 1916], ALS, 2 pp. w/ envelope (Box 16)
- Seymour Hicks to Charles Belmont Davis July 14, 1916, ALS, 3 pp. with envelope (Box 16)
- Booth Tarkington to Charles Belmont Davis August 9, 1916, ALS, 2 pp. with envelope (Box 16)
- F.W.B. Pile to Charles Belmont Davis August 11, 1916, ALS, 2 pp. with envelope (Box 16)
- Anthony Hope Hawkins to Charles Belmont Davis September 9, 1916, ALS, 2 pp. with envelope (Box 16)
- Charles Scribner to [Elizabeth McEvoy] Davis December 1, 1916, ALS, 1 p. (Box 16)
- Guy T. Viskniskki to [Charles Belmont] Davis [1916], ALS, 2 pp. (Box 16)
- Samuel Hopkins Adams to Charles [Belmont Davis] March 1, 1917, ALS, 3 pp. (Box 16)
- Samuel Hopkins Adams to Charles [Belmont Davis] March 21, 1917, ALS, 2 pp. (Box 16)
- Samuel Hopkins Adams to Charles [Belmont Davis] June 18, 1917, ALS, 2 pp. (Box 16)
- Arthur Scribner to Elizabeth McEvoy Davis November 13, 1917, TLS, 2 pp. (Box 16)
- [Rebecca Harding Davis] to [Richard Harding Davis] January 28, n.y., ALS, 6 pp. (Box 16)
- [Rebecca Harding Davis] to [Richard Harding Davis] June 12, n.y., ALS, 4 pp. (Box 16)
- [Rebecca Harding Davis] to [Charles Belmont] Davis July 19, n.y., AL (frag), 4 pp. (Box 16)
- Grover Cleveland to Lemuel Clarke Davis July 24, n.y., Telegram, 1 p. (copy) (Box 16)
- Eugenie Paul Jefferson to [Richard Harding] Davis August 22, n.y., ALS, 2 pp. (Box 16)
- Margaret Deland to [Richard Harding] Davis n.d., ALS, 3 pp. (Box 16)
- [Rebecca Harding Davis] to [Richard Harding Davis] n.d., ALS, 6 pp. (Box 16)
- [Rebecca Harding Davis] to [Richard Harding Davis] n.d., ALS, 4 pp. (Box 16)
- [Rebecca Harding Davis] to [Richard Harding Davis] n.d., ALS, 4 pp. (Box 16)
- [Rebecca Harding Davis] to [Richard Harding Davis] n.d., ALS, 4 pp. (Box 16)
- [Rebecca Harding Davis] to [Richard Harding Davis] n.d., ALS, 4 pp. (Box 16)
- [Rebecca Harding Davis] to [Richard Harding Davis] n.d., ALS, 4 pp. (Box 16)
- [Rebecca Harding Davis] to [Richard Harding Davis] n.d., ALS, 4 pp. (Box 16)
- [Charles] Dana [Gibson] to Richard [Harding Davis] n.d., ALS, 3 pp. (Box 16)
  With a drawing of "Clay's shirt front"
- [Charles] Dana [Gibson] to Charles [Belmont Davis] n.d., ALS, 3 pp. (Box 16)
  With a [self-portrait] drawing, "the way we are feeling..."; an inserted slip reads, "Written February 1897.."